[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Greek mythology, this island is the legendary birthplace of the goddess of beauty, love, and passion, the charming Aphrodite, where according to the legend, she emerged from the sea foam.", "correct_answer": "Cyprus", "incorrect_answers": ["Crete", "Limnos", "Rhodes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Moonbounce is a form of wireless communication in which the moon is used as a passive satellite.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The letter J is the last letter added to the Latin alphabet.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Berjaya Times Square Mall has 45 restaurants, its own theme park , and hip-hop town.  Where is it located?", "correct_answer": "Kuala Lumpur", "incorrect_answers": ["Delhi", "Riyadh", "Bangalore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Freuds psychoanalytic theory, the defense mechanism in which anxiety-producing or unacceptable emotions are replaced by their direct opposites is defined by which term?", "correct_answer": "Reaction formation", "incorrect_answers": ["Hysteria", "Positivism", "Transference"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1965 movie, Thunderball, James Bond is sent to what city, to make contact with Domino?", "correct_answer": "Nassau", "incorrect_answers": ["Trinidad", "Honolulu", "Macau"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2008s Get Smart movie stars Steve Carell, not Don Adams, it does reunite Carell with this co-star of Little Miss Sunshine.", "correct_answer": "Alan Arkin", "incorrect_answers": ["Toni Collette", "Amy Breslin", "Robert Langdon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After Ron hits rock bottom in the comedy hit Anchorman, he is seen walking the streets on a hot day with a full beard and carrying a beverage he regrets choosing.  What is he drinking?", "correct_answer": "Milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Soda", "Beer", "Coffee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the three colours of the national flag of the Netherlands from top to bottom?", "correct_answer": "Red, white, and blue", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue, yellow, and red", "Red, blue, and white", "Green, red, and white"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many toes do ostriches have?", "correct_answer": "Two toes", "incorrect_answers": ["One toe", "Tree toes", "Five toes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what temperature does water begin to boil on top of Mount Everest?", "correct_answer": "150 degrees Fahrenheit", "incorrect_answers": ["212 degrees Fahrenheit", "150 degrees Centigrade", "0 degrees Kelvin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This lawyer-turned senator, who has the power of flight without machinery, is a character on Heroes.", "correct_answer": "Nathan Petrelli", "incorrect_answers": ["Andy Pasdar", "Clark Bennett", "Gabriel Gray"]}]